# SEAN HARRIGAN

## EPIDEMIOLOGIST & RESEARCH SCIENTIST

	NTACT
	<b>ORCiD</b> : 0000-0001-6021-7402
$\boxtimes$	sean.pat.harrigan@gmail.com
	seanharrigan.github.io/website/
<b></b>	Vancouver, BC
SKILLS	
RESE	EARCH METHODS
DAT	A SICENCE
STA	TISTICS
SCIE	NTIFIC WRITING
EDUCATION	
MSc	, Population and Public Health
Univ	ersity of British Columbia
2019	-2021
BSc	
	Biology, Minor Statistics
	Biology, Minor Statistics ersity of Victoria
Univ	
<i>Univ</i> 2013	ersity of Victoria
Univ 2013 C E I	ersity of Victoria -2017
University 2013 CEI	ersity of Victoria -2017 RTIFICATES
University University University University	ersity of Victoria -2017 RTIFICATES hine Learning and AI (2023)
University 2013 CEI Mac University Data	ersity of Victoria -2017 RTIFICATES hine Learning and AI (2023) ersity of Toronto
University	ersity of Victoria -2017 RTIFICATES hine Learning and AI (2023) ersity of Toronto Science (2022) ersity of British Columbia
University Data University L A	ersity of Victoria -2017  RTIFICATES hine Learning and AI (2023) ersity of Toronto Science (2022)
University of the University o	ersity of Victoria -2017  RTIFICATES hine Learning and AI (2023) ersity of Toronto Science (2022) ersity of British Columbia
University Data University L A	ersity of Victoria e-2017  RTIFICATES  hine Learning and AI (2023) ersity of Toronto  Science (2022) ersity of British Columbia  NGUAGES

### ABOUT ME

I am a dedicated and passionate worker who loves to learn. My background includes various research roles related to health in academia, industry and volunteer positions, with a focus in methodology, data / statistical analysis and academic writing. I have a passion for health science research as well as data science, specifically data analysis and data visualisaiton.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Epidemiologist**

BC Centre for Disease Control

2021-Present

- Focused on design and methodology of research projects, data and statistical analysis, and scientific writing
- Conceptualising and conducting all aspects of epidemiologic research studies (i.e. hypotheses, study population, methodology, analysis, etc.)
- Leading the statistical analysis in R, including exploratory analyses as well as creating data analysis pipelines from tidying raw data, applying causal frameworks and to modelling severity outcomes
- Leading the scientific writing of manuscripts for internal use and for publication in scientific journals

## **Researcher & Primary Data Analyst**

University of British Columbia

2020-2021

- Initiative focused in occupational health and safety oh health workers, in Vancouver at the start of the COVID-19 pandemic
- Co-lead a study in collaboration with the World Health
  Organization which surveyed health care workers from around
  world about risks and protection measures in the workplace
  during the pandemic
- Created a database of all physicians and collect data on exposures and test results to monitor physicians and other healthcare workers in Vancouver throughout the pandemic

#### Research Associate

Broadstreet Health Economics and Outcomes Research 2017-2019

- Co-lead a systematic review on a rare disease and have coauthored a meta-analysis on drug effectiveness
- Conducted a systematic literature review and network metaanalysis, including abstract review and data extraction
- Collaborator and pharmaceutical clients in relation to the research projects
- Taken courses from York University in Health Economic Modelling